goair.in 2013-10-21

# GoAir - Privacy Policy

We respect the privacy of our users. This privacy statement is designed to help you understand what information we gather and what we do with the information. The information we collect generally falls into two categories:  

  * Information voluntarily supplied by visitors to our websites through optional registration
  * Tracking information gathered as visitors navigate through our websites.

To make use of certain features of our website (such as e-mail and other interactive forums), visitors need to register and provide certain information as part of the registration process. We may ask, for example, for your name and address, the name and address of your company affiliation, your home and business phone numbers, your e-mail address, certain financial information, and any other information which may be useful. The information you supply will help us to tailor our website to the needs and interests of our visitors.

To help make our website more responsive to the needs and interests of our visitors, we keep track of the pages visited by each user. We aggregate this data with the data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns.

Our web servers automatically collect some information about you when you request pages from our web servers, including your IP address. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the web pages you request) can be sent to you. Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use your IP address to, among other things to help diagnose problems with our web servers, and to administer our website. We may invoke a standard feature of browser software called a "cookie" to better meet the needs of our visitors and to better administer our website. You can set your browser not to accept cookies, but if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of certain personalised features enjoyed by other visitors to our website.

We recognise industry standards and employ security safeguards to protect personal information of our visitors from unauthorised access and misuse. Our online reservation system resides on a secure server that encrypts all purchase information using Secure Socket Layers. We use all reasonable endeavours to protect personal information from loss, misuse and alteration. Only our authorised employees that are under appropriate confidentiality obligations have access to users' personal information.

You should, however, understand that the open nature of the Internet is such that data may flow over networks without security measures and may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended.

Even though we have said it already, the message is important enough to repeat: We respect the privacy of our users. We will NOT sell or provide any of your personal information to any third party except as necessary to provide requisite service(s), carry out the transaction(s) you have requested, to operate the GoAir website and / or if we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

Our website often provides links to third party websites, such as those of our business partners and online advertisers. You should review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why and how they collect and use information of their visitors / users. 

**A final note:** The Web is an evolving medium. We may need to change our privacy policy from time to time. By continuing to use the services after we post such changes, you accept the terms of this policy, as modified.
